<addon id="plugin.video.umbrella" name="Umbrella" provider-name="Umbrella" version="6.6.10">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="context.umbrella" version="1.2.8" optional="true"/>
		<import addon="script.module.cocoscrapers" version="1.0.9"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests"/>
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4"/>
		<import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="5.0.1a" optional="true"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="umbrella.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
		<summary lang="en">[B]Umbrella[/B] - We do not host any of the contents streamed</summary>
		<description lang="en">[B]Umbrella[/B][CR] This addon does not form part of the Kodi Media Centre. Please do not seek assistance with this addon from any of the Official Kodi Support Channels.[CR]The author does not host any of the content in this addon and takes no responsibility for content found. We do not know anything about a lab under Raccoon City.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum/>
		<website>https://umbrellaplug.github.io</website>
		<source>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/umbrellaplug/umbrellaplug.github.io/</source>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot003.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>
[B][COLOR black]Update - v6.6.10 - Jan 21st, 2023[/COLOR][/B]
--[HOTFIX][I] Potential fix for reuselanguageInvoker causing crashes. All credit to TikiPeter![/I]
--[ENHANCEMENT][I] Set trakt recently released trending to use current year only after 6th month of year.[/I]
--[ENHANCEMENT][I] Made codes from authorization auto-copy to clipboard.[/I]
--[ENHANCEMENT][I] Ability to use custom subtitle download path for downloads added by roieeedouek.[/I]
--[ENHANCEMENT][I] Will be used automatically if custom subtitle download folder enabled in Kodi.[/I]
--[NEXUS][I] Added new MyVideos121 into cache detection.[/I]
--[NEXUS][I] Nexus now has a repo.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Added busy spinner when gathering trakt lists for import management window.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Added NoneType condition for playnext issue.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Made Hide Movies in Cinema also hide unreleased movies in all lists.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Sort by date watched fixed for trakt lists.[/I]
--[FIX][I] DirectProgress Scraping combined with Playnext causing skip episode fixed.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Highlight Color instead of hard coded blue now used on codes in prompts for account authorizations.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Added metadatahandler 5.0.1a to repo with fixes for local indicators.[/I]
--[FIX][I] Using local for indicator for watched status now requires a newer version of metahandler due to fixing an issue with metadatahandler exception on cast.[/I]
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>